Amy 即使对你来说 这都太下作了
Amy, this is low, even for you.
难以置信 你们两个都违反了"留在楼下"的规矩
I cannot believe you would both violate the "Please stay downstairs" Rule,
我明明再三强调过的
Which was prominently posted!
快出去
Get outta here!
我不知道为什么还要谈这事
I don't know why we have to have this discussion again.
怎么办
What do we do?
卫生间 卫生间
Bathroom! Bathroom.
你为何生我的气
Why are you upset with me?
你的下属才是派对上最扫兴的人
Your employees are the ones putting a damper on the party.
他们表现糟透了
They are acting terribly.
你才是那个表现糟糕的人
You're the one who's been acting terribly tonight.
对我的客人一副敷衍 自以为是的态度
You've been curt and snobby with my guests.
你一直在刺激(针织)Peralta
You've been needling poor Peralta so much,
都快能给他织出来一套新衣服了
You've practically made him a new suit.